[Music]
as you grow older your aspirations and
responsibilities grow with you to meet
your increasing needs you rely on your
profession or business
but in a world of fluctuating markets
unstable interest rates and sudden job
losses
how do you ensure your financial
security and maintain your standard of
living
how do you create a source of fixed
income that is guaranteed and unaffected
by external circumstances
presenting the icici pro guaranteed
pension plan
an annuity plan that allows you to turn
your savings into financial security in
the form of a guaranteed lifelong income
whether you are a working professional
who doesn't want to depend entirely on
your salary and is looking for an
alternate source of income a businessman
looking to protect himself from the ups
and downs of the business and secure a
guaranteed income a working woman who
wants to secure her financial
independence for the future or simply
someone planning for their retirement
this plan would be great for you
it is also an ideal gift option for
those who wish to ensure the financial
freedom of their parents spouse or
anyone else in their family
with the icici prove guaranteed pension
plan deferred annuity option you can
invest once and choose to start your
lifelong income anytime within the next
10 years this plan allows you to lock in
your future payouts with a single
investment made today the longer you
defer your payouts the higher would be
your fixed payout rate let us understand
the plan better with an example mr gupta
is a 40 year old senior executive at nmc
his wife is 35 years old and they have a
school going son
mr gupta plans to retire at 50 and is
looking for a plan that will ensure
financial security for him and his
family post retirement he decides to
purchase the icici proof guaranteed
pension plan deferred annuity online he
makes a one-time payment of rupees 25
lakhs he chooses to get monthly payouts
and selects the me joint life and
nominee option with his wife as his
joint life and his son as the nominee he
decides to go for the deferred joint
life with return of purchase price
option after 10 years mr gupta will
start getting a regular income of rupees
555 per month this will be paid to him
throughout his life and continued to be
paid to his wife after him and when both
the admittance pass away the purchase
price would be returned to the nominee
this way he will be able to leave behind
a legacy for his son
all these returns are fixed and
risk-free irrespective of unpredictable
market scenarios and unstable interest
rates and that's not all this plan also
gives you tax benefits on the premium
paid under section atccc
with icici proof guaranteed pension plan
deferred annuity you can get multiple
benefits from a single plan making it an
essential component of everyone's
financial portfolio
you can buy the plan easily and securely
from the comfort of your home
buying online also comes with the
benefit of one percent additional
annuity amount payment can be made
through a range of online options
including net banking debit and credit
cards payment wallets and upi
your guaranteed income gets credited
directly to your bank account making the
plan completely safe and hassle free
so what are you waiting for visit icici
prolife.com and ensure lifetime
financial security for yourself in just
a few clicks
you can also consult our insurance
experts for free at 0-2226-295-5609
[Music]